难以置信  我真来做美甲了
You know, I can't believe I'm getting my nails done!
你说会很好玩
And you said it was going to be fun.
倒是真的挺好玩的
Which it kind of is.
你还说会有别的男人来做美甲
Also, you said there would be other guys here.
看看四周  哪儿有啊
There are no other guys here!
钱德勒  那边就有一个
Chandler. There's one right over there.
那是个送信的
That's a mailman!
给我们送信的就是他啊
That's our mailman!
你好...好
Hi, how are you...
钱德勒  放心吧
Chandler, don't worry.
这样无损于你男子气概的
This doesn't make you any less of a guy.
但那样会
That does.
我屁股底下是什么
What am I sitting on?
这女的是抓了哪里
What do you think was this woman scratching
才会弄断这指甲的呀
when this broke off?
知道谁也有这样的指甲吗
You know who used to had nails like that?
我…的…天呐
Oh...my...God!
乔伊  问你一个问题
Joey, let me ask you a question.
我快被这问题逼疯了
It's been driving me crazy.
这个开关是干嘛用的
What does this light switch do?
没用
Nothing.
你不知道它是干嘛的
Didn't it drive you crazy
不会很伤脑筋吗
to have a switch and not know what it did?
我知道啊  它没用
I know what it did. Nothing.
没用就不会装在这里了
They wouldn't have put it there if it didn't do something!
你怎么能不在意
How can you not care?
就像这样
Like this.
还有一个问题
Here's another question for you.
你知道马桶上银色把手的用处吗
Do you know what does the silver knob on the toilet do?
当然知道  冲水啊
Sure, flushes it.
很好  既然你知道
Okay, good. Now that since you know,
下次来用我们厕所时  请你便后冲水好吗
when you come over would you mind actually using it?
大家好
Hello.
天哪
Oh, my God. Wow.
猜猜我们今天碰到谁了
Guess who we ran into today?
-珍妮丝  -很棒吧
- Janice! - Is this amazing?
你过得怎么样
How have you been?
我离婚了
Well, I'm divorced.
现在靠赡养费过活
I'm riding the alimony pony.
又来了
And there it is.
我只是来打声招呼
I just came up to say hi.
-亲爱的  我们待会见  -好
- And you, sweetie, I'll see you later. -OK.
晚上见
I'll see you tonight.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
我受不了那女人
I can't stand the woman!
什么  我还以为你爱死她了
What? I thought you were crazy about her!
但我们相爱前
But you know all those annoying things
她所有讨人厌的小毛病
she did before we fell in love?
她的声音  笑声和个性
Her voice, her laugh and her personality?
全都回来了
They're all back!
而且还多了起码九种新毛病
And she's picked up, like, nine new ones!
那你干嘛带她来  虐待我们啊
Why'd you bring her here? There's people here!
放心  我今晚会搞定
Don't worry about it. I'm taking care of it tonight.
才怪  你一直跟她纠缠不清
You are not! You have never been able to break up with her.
这次我不必跟她分手
I don't have to break up with her this time.
我们还没开始交往呢  我会先发制人
We're not involved. I'll do a preemptive strike.
将我俩的感情扼杀在摇篮里
I'll end it with her before it starts.
我的屁股冷酷如冰  毫无激情
My ass is, like, frozen!
塞进冷冻库20分钟试试看
Try sticking it in the freezer for 20 minutes.
信不信由你
I'm telling you!
你居然敢晚上自己一个人走
I can't believe you walk alone here at night.
据说纽约的治安不太好啊
I mean, you hear such stories about New York.
其实没那么严重
No. It's really not that bad.
我就觉得很安全
I mean, I, for one, feel perfectly safe.
救命啊  救命啊
Help! Help!
罗斯  没事
No, no, Ross!
他们是我在英国的朋友
These are friends from home.
连恩  戴文  这是罗斯
Liam, Devon, this is Ross.
-老兄  -你们好
- Hi, mate. - How are you, man?
我装得不错吧  救命啊  救命啊
That was a good one, huh? "Help! Help!"
你们好吗
How are you?
我一来纽约就想给你们打电话你们
I've been meaning to ring you ever since I arrived...
但是…我挺忙的
but I've been rather busy.
我们从U2演唱会之后
Do you realize, we have not seen each other
就没见过面
since the night of that U2 concert.
天哪  没错
Oh, my God. You're right.
准确地说  你我见最后一次见面
Actually, the last time you and I saw each other
应该是演唱会后第二天早上
was the next morning.
哦  连恩
Oh, Liam!
Oh, Liam.
你们喜欢踢足球吗
So were you guys playing soccer?
或者说是英式足球
Or should I call it "football"?
我们打英式橄榄球
We were playing rugby.
其实明天就有球赛
In fact we're playing a game at the park tomorrow.
欢迎你也来参加
You're welcome to play too if you want.
罗斯打橄榄球  算了吧
Ross play rugby? I don't think so.
有什么可笑的
What's so funny about that?
首先  你是个美国人
Well, you're American to start with.
你们压根不玩橄榄球
You don't have rugby here.
我们这里在1776年以前  还没有自由呢
Well, we didn't have freedom here until 1776 either, so...
那好  明天下午两点河畔公园见
So good then! We'll see you at Riverside Park at 2:00!
干杯
Cheers!
天哪  我最喜欢唱歌了
Oh, boy! I just love to sing.
我知道你喜欢
Yes, I know that you do.
而现场其他人之所以怨声载道
but I think one of the reasons people were complaining though...
是因为他们以前是要花钱
is because most people paid to hear the actor
才能听演员唱《老人河》呢
sing "Old Man River".
看看我们
Look at us!
想不到在美容院也有爱神驻扎
Who would've thought Cupid had a station at 14th Street Nails?
我们得谈谈
Okay, we have to talk.
我刚结束了一段很认真投入的恋情
I'm just getting out of a very serious relationship.
我知道  而我刚结束一段婚姻
I know. And I'm just getting out of a marriage.
这就叫作"三生注定"
Talk about "meant to be."
对  但我觉得进展太快了
Right. But I just think this is happening too soon.
什么太快  哪里快了
Oh, too soon, too schmoon!
认命吧  这次我绝不会让你跑掉的
Face it, honey, I'm not letting you get away this time.
我听见了
I hear you!
但是
But...
很不幸的是
unfortunately...
我的公司
my company...
要把我调到海外
is transferring me overseas.
不会吧
Oh, no!
调去哪里
Where to?
巴黎吗
To Paris?
不  不是巴黎
No, not Paris.
伦敦  罗马  维也纳
To London? Rome? Vienna?
巴塞罗纳
Barcelona?
你先别讲话好吗
Could you just stop talking for a second?
也门
Yemen.
对  没错  我要被调去也门
That's right. Yes! I'm being transferred to Yemen!
什么时候
When?
还没定
I don't know exactly.
那我只能如胶似漆地缠着
Well, I will just have to soak up every ounce...
钱德勒·宾  直到那一刻来临
of Chandler Bing until that moment comes.
但明天我肯定要走
But I do know it's sometime tomorrow.
-好了  -对
- Done? - Yep!
怎么了
What's up?
这个开关快把我逼疯了
This switch thing is driving me crazy.
所以我关掉开关  检查了每个插座
So, I turned it off and checked every outlet.
有四个不能用
Four don't work,
说明其中一个由它控制
which means one of them has to controlled by the switch.
所以  我在那四个插座上
So, I plugged in things
都插上了能发声的东西
in all four of the outlets that-that make noise.
到时候一开开关  我就顺着声音去找
That way, when I turn it on, I just follow the noise.
就知道开关控制的是哪个插座了
And find out which one of them it is.
我肯定会比你先放弃
I bet I stopped listening before you did.
其实你可以插电灯的...
You know, you also could have used lamps...
然后看哪里亮起来了
and followed the light.
可我要喜欢顺着声音找
Yeah, well, I'm using noise.
好了  大家准备好了吗
All right! So, is everybody ready?
开始了
Here we go!
有声音  我听到了  在哪里
Something. I hear something. Where is it?
是乔伊发出来的
It's coming from Joey!
天哪  好诡异  快把他关掉
Oh, my God! That's so freaky! Turn him off!
可以看新闻吗
Ooh, hey, could we put on the news?
外面可能会下雨
I think it might be raining.
稍等一下
Oh, just hold on a second.
我在看ESPN转播的橄榄球赛
I'm watching this rugby thing on ESPN.
有什么了不起啊
I don't know what the big deal is.
我也是个男人  这我也能打
I'm man enough to play this sport.
你是男人
Dude, you're not even man enough
可你连运动频道都没订
to order the channel that carries the sport.
你好  罗斯
Hey there, Ross!
是珍妮丝
Janice.
你真的不必帮我收拾行李
You know, you really didn't have to help me pack.
是你说  你出发之前的时间
when you said all you were going to be doing
都得用来收拾行李
between now and the time you leave is packing,
我还有什么选择呢
you really didn't leave me much choice, did you?
我以为有很多东西  不过看来没多少
I thought I did, but I guess I did not.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我要得收拾行李  我收拾行李...
I'm packing, Y'know I'm-I'm packing...
是因为我明天要去也门
cause I'm moving to Yemen tomorrow.
多谢你告诉我啊
Thanks for telling me!
我是假装要去也门
I'm only pretend to moving to Yemen,
好摆脱她
it's the only way I can get rid off her.
好主意
Good one!
也门  真会编  听起来还真像个国家名呢
Yemen! That actually sounds like a real country!
钱德勒  快来
Chandler! Come on,
我教你怎么把内衣裤卷起来塞进鞋子
I'll show you how to roll your underwear and stuff it in your shoes.
可以节省空间
It's a real space-saver.
我知道  不过我那样做是想显得高一点
Yeah, I know, I do that because it makes me look taller.
钱德勒  来啊
Chandler! Come on!
-乔伊  跟我交换人生  -不要
- Joey, trade lives with me. - Nope.
天呐  罗斯
Man look at this! Ross,
你居然要打橄榄球
I can't believe you said you'd play rugby.
这种运动多野蛮
I mean look how brutal this is!
我没问题的  相信我
Hey, I can handle it! All right?
拜托  罗斯  你跟我爸打羽毛球都会受伤
Please, Ross. You got hurt playing badminton with my dad.
那是因为你妈的狗一直瞪着我
That's because your mom's dog kept looking at me.
罗斯  你看  看这里
Okay, Ross, look, look right here.
这个叫作"并列争球"
That's called a scrum, okay?
一堆人挤作一团抢球
It's like a huddle.
不就是个球吗  有什么好抢的
And is a hum, kinda like a scruddle?
罗斯  他们会要了你命的
Ross, they're going kill you!
你到底为什么要打橄榄球啊
Why are you doing this, anyway?
你们应该看看她以前交往的人
You should've seen the guys she used to go out with.
那人活像颗"巨型橄榄球"
He's like "Joe Rugby"!
"巨型橄榄球"打橄榄球  好搞笑
You're kidding! And he plays rugby? That's funny!
我懂你的意思了  是比喻
Oh, I see. You did that.
总之  她觉得我和那个男的
Anyway, she thought the very idea of
一起打橄榄球很好笑
me playing rugby with him was like hilarious.
所以我要证明我有多猛
So I'll show her how tough I really am.
对不起  你说得对  你是很猛
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You're right, you are a tough guy.
你是我认识最猛的古生物学家
The toughest paleontologist just I know.
没问题啦  罗斯会照顾好自己的
All right, come on look, Ross can take care of himself!
他又不是...钱德勒
It's not like he's...Chandler!
谢了
Thanks.
别替我担心
Don't worry about me.
我会装得很有冲劲  跟球保持距离
I'll just look real energetic and stay away from the ball.
我会学那个人  站在圈外
I'll be that guy, right outside the circle.
也许有狗在瞪着他
Maybe there was a dog looking at him.
罗斯  别靠近那个  那个还有那个人
Ross, stay away from that guy and that guy and that one...
他们都好壮
Dude, they're all huge!
又没比我壮
They don't look any bigger than me!
可能因为你离自己比较近
Well, maybe that's because you're closer to you.
所以觉得自己比较壮
So you look bigger to you from where you are.
我去跟他们打个招呼
I'm just going to say hi to the lads. All right?
好的
All right.
他挺招人喜欢的
I kinda liked it.
我知道怎么办了
Okay, I know what I have to do.
我要变成"赤面罗斯"
I've got to go Red Ross.
赤面罗斯啊
You know, Red Ross?
我完全不知道你在讲什么
Totally don't know what you are talking about.
那次我们一起排队
Come on, that time we were all waiting in line
去买《与狼共舞》的票...
for Dances With Wolves...
有人插队  我不是就抓狂了
and that one guy cut in front of us and I just lost it?
破口大骂  脸都涨红了
Screamed at him, turned all red!
就是那个赤面罗斯
Red Ross!
等着瞧
You'll see!
连恩  帮个忙
Liam, do me a favor.
让大家对罗斯手下留情
Tell the lads to go easy on Ross,
他第一次玩橄榄球
it's his first time.
完全看不出来嘛
You don't say?
加油  亲爱的
Good luck, babe.
罗斯  快过来  到这儿来
Ross! Ross! Come on! Get in here!
快点
Come on!
罗斯  挤到人堆里来
Ross! Come on, get in the bloody scrum!
罗斯  进去
Ross, get in!
乔伊
Joey!
说出来你都不信
You are not going to believe it!
约书亚今天过来  猜猜发生了什么
Joshua came into work today, and guess what happened?
-他约你出去了吗  -没有
- He asked you out? - No.
不过我给他挑袖扣  顺便摸了他的脉搏
But I was showing him some cuff links, and I felt his pulse.
干得漂亮
Saucy!
这是什么
What are these?
这栋楼的电路图
Electrical plans for the building.
你到底想干什么
Okay, should I be scared?
那个开关一定是有什么用的
I know that switch is gonna do something, okay?
这是去市政府调的
So I went down to city hall and got these.
只花了25元  排了3小时队
All I had to do was pay $25 and wait in line for three hours.
还好知道的人不多
Wow! If only more people knew!
你实在不必送我来机场
You really didn't have to take me to the airport.
拜托  每分每秒都很珍贵
Oh, please. Every moment is precious.
而且总得有人搭乘另一辆出租车
Besides, somebody had to ride in that other taxi
帮你看着另一半行李吧
with the rest of your luggage
你的那些朋友好像
And your friends don't seem to care very much
根本不在乎你离开似的
that you're leaving.
其实我们关系不是很好
We're not really that close.
好  我们就此告别吧
Okay. So I guess this is goodbye then.
不
Oh, no!
我才不走  我会一直陪到你上飞机为止
It's not goodbye. I'm not leaving till you get on that plane.
好  那就"请在此等候"
Okay. Well, I guess it's just "wait here" then.
我要一张去也门的假机票
I need a fake ticket to Yemen.
一张去也门的机票吗
One ticket?
我只需要一张假机票
I just need a pretend ticket.
抱歉  先生  我不太明白
I'm sorry sir, I don't understand.
小孩想要张票玩的时候
What would you give to a kid
你会给他什么
if he wanted a ticket to play with?
您带了小孩子一起坐飞机吗
Are you traveling with a child?
没有
No.
她会以为我在拿信用卡给你
She'll think I'm handing you a credit card.
其实我给你的是借书证
But what I'll really hand you is a library card.
去也门的机票2100美元
Sir, a ticket to Yemen is $2100,
而且我们不收借书证
and we don't take library cards.
怎么了  有什么问题吗
What's the matter? Is something wrong?
你要去不成了吗
Do you have to stay?
美国运通卡收吗
American Express?
他们怎么这样
I can't believe they're doing that to him!
我明明叫他们手下留情
I told them to go easy on him!
我没别的意思
No offense, but sometimes it's hard
但有时你的口音的确很难懂
to understand you, you know, with the accent.
才上半场结束  还有下半场
That's just halftime. There's more of this.
你们看到了吗
Did you see me?
我玩得真好  好过瘾的球赛
I was pretty good. That is one fun game!
帮个忙
Could you do me a favour?
请帮我拿瓶水好吗
Just grab me a bottle of water?
谢谢
Thanks!
我觉得我快死了  真的
I think I'm dying. I really do.
真可怜
Poor baby!
告诉我儿子我爱他
Tell my son that I love him.
太好了  我还要再打个过瘾
Excellent! Got to have some more fun!
罗斯  你快被整死了
They are killing you out there.
乱讲
That's not true.
她说得对  你不能再打了
She's right. You have to stop!
不行  我是赤面罗斯
No! I'm not stopping. I'm Red Ross!
你再上场会变成死面罗斯了
Dude, you go back out there, you'll be Dead Ross.
我绝不退场
I don't care, I'm not quitting.
我要坚持到底
I'm going to finish this game.
如果你一定要打
All right, all right, if you insist on doing this,
至少让我帮帮忙吧
at least let me help you.
不行  这可不是女人玩的
No, God no! That is no place for a woman.
那些人什么都抓
Those guys will grab anything.
我不是要上场
No. That's not what I'm saying.
我只是想告诉你
I just may know a few things
怎样让别人受伤
that might help you inflict some pain.
这个我喜欢
I like that.
听好了
Listen closely.
戴文的脚踝很弱
Devon has got a weak ankle.
踢一下就会倒
One swift kick and he'll back off.
踢脚踝  明白
Bad ankle. Got it!
那个落腮胡的大个子  髋部受过伤
And that big bloke with the beard? He's got a trick hip.
那个大卫  听说没戴护膝
And David over there, I heard he doesn't wear a cup.
明白了  髋部不好  没穿护膝  没问题
I could use that. Trick hip, no cup. Okay!
还有连恩  他膝盖不好
And Liam's got bad knees.
看准地方下手  一撞就倒
You hit him right and he'll go down like a lamp.
但是连恩是我队友
But Liam's on my team.
-我不管  你去宰了他  -宰了他
- I don't care. You just get him! - Go and get him!
我要回场上了
I am going back in!
真的是赤面罗斯
Red Ross! Yeah!
这些是什么
What are these?
我画了一些画挂起来
Just some pictures I made and hung up.
这下客厅更漂亮了
I thought they'd brighten up the place.
不觉得吗
They do don't you think?
别别别
No-no-no, no!
那里没有洞
I know there's no hole there.
我只是很喜欢那幅画
I just really like that picture.
天哪  你看
Oh, my God! Look at this!
那开关后面有线
Okay, but there is a wire back there!
肯定连着什么地方
I mean that switch is connected to something!
我才不在乎  这些线已经让你脑子短路了
I don't care! The wires have come loose in your head!
我只想沿着电线顺藤摸瓜
I just thought that if I could follow the wire
找出开关的功用
I could find out what it did.
那你找到了吗
And did you?
没有
No.
线走到那层夹板后面就消失了
It disappears back there behind that baseboard.
跟凯卓奇斯太太打个招呼吧
Say hello to Mrs. Catrokis.
亲爱的  你好啊
Hello, darling.
凯卓奇斯太太  你好
Hello, Mrs. Catrokis.
凯卓奇斯太太  你认识Kenny吗
Hey, Mrs. Catrokis, do you know Kenny?
你不是开玩笑吧...
You've got to be kidding...
你真的不去看医生吗
Are you sure you don't want go and see a doctor?
不要  那样多丢人啊
No, that'll just bring me down!
太棒了  我太厉害了  今天真过瘾
This was great! I was great! This was a great day!
我请大家喝咖啡
You know what, I'm buying everyone coffee.
帮我拿皮夹  在我的口袋里
Can someone just grab my wallet. It's in my pocket.
-没问题  -没说你
- Yeah, sure. - No, not you.
你的眼睛还有些肿
Your eye's still popping out a little there.
我去拿冰块
I'll go get some ice.
冰块  我正想吃冰块
Ice, yeah! I'm so in the mood for ice.
你刚才好神勇
You were amazing out there.
确实蛮神勇的吧
I kind of was, wasn't I?
老天啊
Oh, my God!
我让一个壮我两倍的人哭了
I made a man twice my size cry!
上一次干出这种事还是4岁的时候
I haven't done that since I was 4
那次我用石头洗我爸的宝时捷
and I washed my dad's Porsche with rocks.
你真的打得很过瘾  对不对
You really enjoyed yourself, didn't you?
开玩笑  我干掉三个大块头
Please, are you kidding? I hurt three huge men.
还让一个人流鼻血
I gave a guy a bloody nose!
虽说这没什么好得意的
I'm not proud of it...
不过  我真的好得意
but I really am!
这都归功于你
And it's all because of you.
最完美  最神奇的你
Wonderful, amazing you.
我看你是脑震荡了
I think you've got a concussion.
不  我是说真的  谢谢你
No, I'm serious. Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
对不起  痛吗
I'm sorry. Did that hurt you?
痛也值得
It's worth the pain.
还是等不痛了再抱吧
You know what? It's not.
最后一次呼叫前住也门664航班的旅客
This is the final boarding call for flight 664 to Yemen.
看来我该走了
Well, I guess I gotta go.
我的宾心肝
My Bing-a-ling.
我会等你的
I'll wait for you.
你知道要去多久吗
Do you even know how long you're going to be gone?
等找到能代替燃料的新能源就回来
Well, just until we find an energy source to replace fuel.
我会每天给你写信的
I'll write you every day.
也门国  也门路15号
15 Yemen Road, Yemen.
再见  你回去吧
Okay. Goodbye.
-钱德勒  -不是我
- Chandler! - No.
钱德勒
Chandler!
珍妮丝  终于找到你了
Janice! There you are!
我得跟你最后吻别一下
I had to have one last kiss.
另外你也说我一上机  你就要走的
And also, you said you'd leave right after I got on the plane!
不  我想看着你起飞
No. I want to see you take off.
好吧  看来我非去也门不可了
Well, then I guess I'm going to Yemen.
我要去也门了
I'm going to Yemen!
到了也门  我可以住你家吗
When we get to Yemen, can I stay with you?
好了  管理员不知道它的作用
All right. The super couldn't figure out what it did.
每小时工资两百的电工不晓得它的作用
The $200-an-hour electrician couldn't figure out what it did.
我被狠狠地电到了七次
I've had seven pretty serious shocks.
我宣布  我放弃了
I officially give up.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
看来乔伊说得对
I guess Joey was right.
它就是没用
It does nothing.
你看
See?
我能控制屏幕  真的能
I'm doing it! I am totally doing it!
超能力没了
I lost it.